<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
    <meta type="array">
        <description>CSH for mail2news importer records</description>
        <type>CSH</type>
        <csh_table>tx_mail2news_importer</csh_table>
        <fileId>EXT:mail2news/locallang_csh_importer.xml</fileId>
    </meta>
    <data type="array">
        <languageKey index="default" type="array">
        <!-- The first label .description will be shown next to the table in list module -->
            <label index=".description">Configuration options for mail-to-news importers</label>
            <label index="allowed_senders.description">Enter allowed from-email-addresses or part of the email addresses, comma separated. '@' allowes all email addresses.</label>
            <label index="title.description">This field has no function except for yourself, to identify this record.</label>
            <label index="override_sections.description">The default settings are set in the Extension Manager. Here you can choose which fields you want to change for this specific importer</label>
            <label index="use_ssl.description">Enable only if your mailserver supports this</label>
            <label index="self_signed_certificate.description">If your mailserver uses a self-signed SSL certificate you can allow this here</label>
            <label index="portno.description">Leave 0 or empty to use defaults</label>
            <label index="delete_after_download.description">Delete messages from email account after they are succesfully processed</label>
            <label index="delete_rejected_mail.description">Also delete messages that where rejected because of sender not in allowed senders or other reason. Do not use this on a shared email account!</label>
            <label index="concatenate_text_parts.description">In the default setting only the first text part is imported, which skips separate signature parts. Check this box to import and concatenate all text parts of multi-part messages.</label>
            <label index="imageextensions.description">Comma separated list of image extensions, like png,jpg,gif. Files with extensions used here will be filtered to news images and will NOT end up at the news file attachments.</label>
            <label index="attachmentextensions.description">Comma separated list of file extensions, like pdf,odt,doc, etc.</label>
            <label index="record_type.description">Mail2news can create news and blog records for the extensions tt_news and t3blog. You can only choose the options for which the extensions are installed (tt_news or t3blog)</label>
            <label index="default_category.description">Title or ID of default ttnews category for news items created by this extension, used if no (valid) category has been set in email message.</label>
            <label index="default_t3blog_category.description">Title or ID of default t3blog category for blog items created by this extension, used if no (valid) category has been set in email message.</label>
            <label index="news_cruser_id.description">ID of the backend user to whom the created records will be assigned.</label>
            <label index="hide_by_default.description">If checked, new records will only show on the website after a backend user unhides them.</label>
            <label index="clearcachecmd.description">Comma separated list of page IDs where the created content will be shown, of which the cache should be cleared for the new items to be shown.</label>
        </languageKey>
    </data>
</T3locallang>